Dan Ogrodnik

Dan.Ogrodnik@gmail.com www.DanOgrodnik.com

Profile:

Front-end Developer, Audio Engineer, former C-level executive of a multinational talent provider, and educator with a background in web design and e-commerce. Skills include HTML/CSS, JavaScript, Python, Ruby, and specializes in React. Prior experience in sales, fundraising, event production, staffing, and customer service. Classically trained musician with strong analysis and memorization skills, and ability to learn new systems quickly. Experienced with DAWs, audio engineering, recording, live sound, lighting, event production, streaming, management, and education K-12 undergrad and post-grad. Fluent in music theory and notation software.

Education:

MFA, Music 2013 California Institute of the Arts, Valencia, CA BM, Music 2009 Hartt School of Music, University of Hartford, CT

Current Occupations:

Staff Accompanist

USC Glorya Kaufman School of Dance 05/2016 – present

Web Developer

Self-Employed 05/2013 – present www.DanOgrodnik.com

Previous Experience:

Chief Operating Officer

Concert Talent 07/2014 - 01/2017

- COO of a multinational talent provider handling large-scale event production
- Produced 350+ events in a 3-month period with MAC Cosmetics Magic of the Night campaign

Faculty, Stage Production

AGBU Vatche and Tamar Manoukian High School 05/2017 – 08/2020

- Stage instructor for high schoolers including lights, live sound, recording, scenic design, stage management, concert production, woodworking, and more
- Audio, lighting, stage technician for independent events
- Ran an extracurricular music club with ensembles that performed live at Rose Bowl festivities

Artist Department

LA Philharmonic, Hollywood Bowl 05/2013 – 09/2015

- Additional positions held with Ticket Sales and Fundraising
- First and last point of contact between performing artists and the Los Angeles Philharmonic
- · Coordinated artist transportation to and from airports, hotels, rehearsals, performances, and more
- Performance equipment cartage